A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Research and Evaluation, SG 3, Series 12 FA791
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Research and Evaluation, SG 3, Series 12
1991-2000
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA791
6.65 Cubic Feet 17 letter document boxes and 1 half-box
Scope and Contents
Primarily contains documentation of surveys including statistics, methodology and research, as well as their resulting banner books. The surveys represented in this series include but are not limited to the Women's Health Survey (Adolescent Girls and Boys), the New York City Health Care Survey, Low Income and Access to Care, Doctors in Managed Care, the Workers Health Insurance Survey, and the Future of Medicaid (Kaiser Commission) reports.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
As received.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Commonwealth Fund records were donated to RAC in 1985. Record transfers began in 1986, and accruals continue. This material was transferred to RAC in 2001 and 2007, as accession 2001:051 and accession 2007:055.
- Research and Evaluation, 1991-2000; 12; 6.65 Cubic Feet 17 letter document boxes and 1 half-box
  - Five Nations Banner Books - Summary Books, 1998 September 29 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Australia, Canada, New Zealand, United Kingdom, United States
  - Five Nations Banner Books - Demographics I, 1998 September 29 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Five Nations Banner Books - Demographics II, 1998 September 29 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Five Nations Banner Books - Health Status, 1998 September 29 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Women's Health Survey II - Final Tabulations - Banner 1 and 2 - Mens Demographics, 1998 December (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Survey of Women's Health (Adolescent Girls and Boys, Grant 96956) - Instrument (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Survey of Women's Health (Adolescent Girls and Boys, Grant 96956) - Fact Sheet Draft (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Survey of Women's Health (Adolescent Girls and Boys, Grant 96956) - KD and CS Papers, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Survey of Women's Health (Adolescent Girls and Boys, Grant 96956) - Checked Press Packet, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Survey of Women's Health (Adolescent Girls and Boys, Grant 96956) - Charts and Supporting Studies, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
  - Survey of Women's Health (Adolescent Girls and Boys, Grant 96956) - Adolescent Book - Preliminary, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Survey of Women's Health (Adolescent Girls and Boys, Grant 96956) - Depression, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Survey of Women's Health (Adolescent Girls and Boys, Grant 96956) - Literature Review, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Survey of Women's Health (Adolescent Girls and Boys, Grant 96956) - Requests for Data, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Survey of Women's Health (Adolescent Girls and Boys, Grant 96956) - Final Release Materials, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Survey of Women's Health (Adolescent Girls and Boys, Grant 96956) - Adolescent Boys Survey, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Low Income Survey (Grant 95605) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - National Survey of Adults Mentoring Young People (Grant 970945) (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
  - Medicare and Managed Care Survey (Grant 970152) (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Kaiser-Commonwealth Fund Health Insurance Survey, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Kaiser-Commonwealth Fund Health Insurance Survey, 1993-1997 (Box 4, Folder 23-25)
  - New York City Health Care Survey (Grant 96003), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - New York City Health Care Survey (Grant 96003) - Data Runs, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - New York City Health Care Survey (Grant 96003) - Kids Talk, 1997 December 10 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - New York City Health Care Survey (Grant 96003) - Kids Talk - Presentation Slides, 1997 December 10; 2001:051:001; 25 slides (Box SF1)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Separated materials are restricted from access until they have been stabilized.
  - New York City Health Care Survey (Grant 96003) - Kids Talk, 1997 December 10 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - New York City Health Care Survey (Grant 96003) - Charts, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - New York City Health Care Survey (Grant 96003) - Memos, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Parents Survey, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 32-33)
  - Parents Survey, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Women's Health Commission - Managed Care and Women's Health, 1998 January 28 (Box 6, Folder 35-36)
  - MEM Symposium - Literature, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 37-38)
    - MEM Symposium - Literature - Presentation Slides, 1998; 2001:051:002; 24 slides (Box SF1)
  - MEM Symposium - Tables, Papers and Surveys, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Workers Health Insurance Survey (Grant 980775) - Administration, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Workers Health Insurance Survey (Grant 980775) - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Workers Health Insurance Survey (Grant 980775) - Grant Products, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Workers Health Insurance Survey (Grant 980775) - Proposal Development, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Workers Health Insurance Survey (Grant 980775) - Questionnaire Development, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 44-46)
  - Workers Health Insurance Survey (Grant 980775) - Methodology and Final Questionnaire, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Workers Health Insurance Survey (Grant 980775) - Tabulations Specifications, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Workers Health Insurance Survey (Grant 980775) - Survey Meeting, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Workers Health Insurance Survey (Grant 980775) - Bids, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 50-51)
  - Health Confidence Survey (PDF 20000645), 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Contingent Workers and the Labor Market (PDF 990913) - Ken Thorpe, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Economy on Employer Provided Health Insurance (Grant 96008) - Tulane (Thorpe) - Administration, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Economy on Employer Provided Health Insurance (Grant 96008) - Tulane (Thorpe) - Articles (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Economy on Employer Provided Health Insurance (Grant 96008) - Tulane (Thorpe) - Grant Products, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Economy on Employer Provided Health Insurance (Grant 96008) - Tulane (Thorpe) - Papers, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Economy on Employer Provided Health Insurance (Grant 96008) - Tulane (Thorpe) - Papers, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 58-59)
  - Joint Israel - Women's Health Survey in Israel (PDF 97082), 1998 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Health Council Development Meeting (PDF 2000064), 1999 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - National Survey of Mid-Sized and Large Employees - Gabel (PDF 990219), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 62-63)
  - Low Income and Access to Care - Tabulations - Book 1 of 2 (Study No. 942016), 1996 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Doctors in Managed Care Tabulations (Study No. 942018), 1996 (Box 10, Folder 66-67)
  - Low Income and Access to Care in Minnesota, Oregon, Tennessee, Florida and Texas (Study No. 942016), 1996 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Louis Harris and Associates, Inc. - Grantees Tabulations (Study No. 934003), 1993 October (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Low Income and Access to Care - Tabulations - Book 2 of 2 (Study No. 942016), 1996 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Low Income and Access to Care - 5 States - Final Tabulations - Banners 1 and 2 (Study No. 942016), 1996 July 23 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Low Income and Access to Care - 5 States - Final Tabulations - Banners 5-6 (Study No. 942016), 1996 July 23 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Low Income and Access to Care - 5 States - Final Tabulations - Banner 7 (Study No. 942016), 1996 July 23 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Health Care Services and Minority Groups - A Comparative Survey (Study No. 93028), 1994 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Dropping Out - A Pilot Survey of Young African American Males (Study No. 902066), 1994 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - The Importance of Choice in Medicaid Home Care Programs: Maryland, Michigan and Texas (Study No. 902064), 1991 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Health Care in Three Nations - The Views of Physicians in the U.S., Canada and (West) Germany (Study No. 902028) (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - The Future of Medicaid - Kaiser Commission - Reports, 1995-1997 (Box 13, Folder 78-81)
  - Doctors in Managed Care - Tabulations - Group/Staff Model HMO (Unweighted) (Study No. 942018), 1996 (Box 14, Folder 82)
  - Doctors in Managed Care - Tabulations (No Managed Care) (Study No. 942018), 1996 (Box 14, Folder 83)
  - Doctors in Managed Care - Tabulations (Managed Care Contracts) (Study No. 942018), 1996 (Box 14, Folder 84)
  - Low Income and Access to Care - Preliminary Tabulations - Banner by Banner (Book 1 of 8) (Study No. 942016) (Box 14, Folder 85)
  - Low Income and Access to Care - Preliminary Tabulations - Banners 1 and 2 (Study No. 942016) (Box 15, Folder 86)
  - Low Income and Access to Care - Preliminary Tabulations - Banner 4 (Book 5 of 8) (Study No. 942016) (Box 15, Folder 87)
  - Doctors in Managed Care - Tabulations - Minority Physicians (Unweighted) (Study No. 940218), 1996 (Box 15, Folder 88)
  - Americans and Their Health Insurance II - Tabulations (Study No. 932010) (Box 15, Folder 89)
  - Challenges in Health Care - A Chartbook Perspective, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 90)
  - Americans and Their Healthcare Experiences - Tabulations (Study No. 912063) (Box 16, Folder 91)
  - A Comparative Analysis of the Presidential Candidates Health Plans, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 92)
  - Executive Vice President's Report on Major Programs, 1993-1995 (Box 16, Folder 93)
  - Partnership for a Drug Free America - New York Inner City Program, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 94)
  - Low Income and Access to Care - Preliminary Tabulations, 1995 October 10 (Box 16, Folder 95)
  - Low Income and Access to Care - Final Banner Tabulations - Book 1 of 3 (Study No. 942016) (Box 16, Folder 96)
  - Low Income and Access to Care - 5 States - Final Tabulations - Banner by Banner (Study No. 942016), 1996 July 23 (Box 16, Folder 97)
  - Low Income and Access to Care - 5 States - Final Tabulations - Banners 3 and 4 (Study No. 942016), 1996 July 23 (Box 17, Folder 98)
  - Low Income and Access to Care - Final Banner Tabulations - Book 2 of 3 (Study No. 942016) (Box 17, Folder 99)
  - Low Income and Access to Care - Final Banner Tabulations - Book 3 of 3 (Study No. 942016) (Box 17, Folder 100)